(Raj:)So, where's
your roommate tonight?
(Emily:)Well, I thought it
was a little unfair
(Emily:)that she's always here,
and you never
(Emily:)get a chance to stay over,
so... I killed her.
(Raj:)But remember our agreement?
(Raj:)You can joke
about murdering people,
(Raj:)but you have to say,
"Just kidding."
(Emily:)And the more important
thing to remember is
(Emily:)that I'd never hurt you.
(phone chimes)
(Emily:)Oh, crap.
(Emily:)I have to run over to the
hospital and check on a patient.
(Raj:)That's okay.
I can come back later.
No.
(Emily:)No, don't be silly.
(Emily:)I won't be gone long.
Just stay here.
(Raj:)Okay, cool.
(Raj:)Oh, and you're sure
your roommate's
(Raj:)not gonna come back
while I'm here alone, right?
'Cause that'll be awkward.
(Emily:)Oh, don't worry.
She's in Palm Springs.
(Sheldon:)Oh, good.
(Emily:)Well, her torso is.
(Raj:)Just kidding.
(Emily:)I put her in a wood chipper.